Hello.
That actually one more thing going to add to our air.
We've made it through that.
I can detect if there's something in front of it.
And if there is, then I'll turn around.
However, if I remove these walls and I'm just going to shrink this platform, so I'm just going to
scale that down a bit.
I'm just going to slap my eye and move it back a bit.
If I just go straight, I will continue walking.
It doesn't know when it's on the edge of the world.
It'll just walk off the edge and die.
We need to make it so, and I can detect whether it's on the edge and if it's on an edge for turnaround.
So if we head back to our Scantron and blueprint, and I'm just going to common all these nodes, so
it's a bit tidier and I'll call this detect whether something is in front of our Scantron.
Then after add movement input, we just want to drag off this node and look for sequence.
So the way a sequence will work first or for this node, then you'll fire at this node.
We just want to copy all these nodes and paste them here and pick up from then one to here.
I'm just going to double click to make this a bit tidier.
And this time we're going to do a line phrase, which is a couple of units in front of our actor and
around here to basically detect whether there is some edge in front of us.
So over here we just drag and subtract.
And in the Z, we're going to put a value of 102 circles up here.
So what this line tries will be doing first, it'll start wherever actor is, but it's going to end
100 units beneath our character and 100 units in front of them.
So roughly around here.
And the way this will work, as long as this is firing true, that means there's ground below our character.
However, if this is false, that means there's no more ground beneath our character.
You'll visually see what I mean in the moment over time.
Just drag up here and look for Branch.
So if this is false, that means there's no more edge in front of us.
We want all Scampton to turn around.
So over false.
I'm going to hook into our.
Do you want.
And I'm just going to turn off the duration here and make sure this is turned on here.
If we now go compile and save and I close this, if I go simulate, we can see my line trace.
As long as there's ground in front of us, this will go green.
However, if I reach the edge, that last line is red.
So it means there's no more ground in front of us.
So my Scampton stopped and then turned around.
So now I'll scan to know when it's on the edge of a world or if there's an object in front of us.
So there's a bit more clever to keep things tidy.
I'm just going to come.
All the nodes I've made so far so common.
All these nodes detect whether Scampton is on the edge of a world.
I am going to comment this node handle rotation.
And I'm going to come in.
All these nodes handle movement.
We can compile and say.